<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>alexander_ruf</title><link>https://www.alexruf.net/</link><description>Recent content on alexander_ruf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 15:05:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.alexruf.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy Gitea and Woodpecker CI with Docker Compose</title><link>https://www.alexruf.net/posts/deploy-gitea-woodpecker-docker-compose/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 15:05:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.alexruf.net/posts/deploy-gitea-woodpecker-docker-compose/</guid><description>Just a short post to let you know that I published my instructions on Codeberg on how to quickly set up your own self-hosted Gitea server with Woodpecker CI and Traefik as a reverse proxy on your own local home server.
Docker Compose Traefik Docker Compose Gitea Docker Compose Woodpecker CI with Gitea integration I have split everything up into individual Docker Compose files. You can also put everything together into on big Docker Compose if you like, but I prefer my components to be serperated nicely.</description></item><item><title>How to Setup WireGuard VPN</title><link>https://www.alexruf.net/posts/how-to-setup-wireguard-vpn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 22:17:45 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.alexruf.net/posts/how-to-setup-wireguard-vpn/</guid><description>WireGuard has become a popular VPN protocol due to its simplicity and security. I created this guide because as a non-Linux administrator and non-network professional, I found it quite difficult to find correct and complete instructions on how to set up my own VPN with WireGuard. The official documentation didn&amp;rsquo;t help me much in this either.
WireGuard Server and Client The goal here is to set up a WireGuard server on Ubuntu Server 20.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.alexruf.net/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.alexruf.net/about/</guid><description>My name is Alexander Ruf and I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer interested in coding, open source, software engineering and tons of other stuff.
I&amp;rsquo;m located in Germany.
If you want to contact me, you can reach me via email or find me on GitHub and Codeberg.</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>https://www.alexruf.net/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.alexruf.net/archive/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>